Guide to the Locus Science Fiction Foundation archives, 1942-2012 RL.11689
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Name Files
  - Finlay, Beverly, 1979 (Box 3)
  - Fintushel, Eliot, undated (Box 3)
  - Fisher, Paul, undated (Box 3)
    "Self-Portrait in Ink"
  - Flint, Kenneth, 1987 (Box 3)
    Book cover for "Storm Shield," interview in Waldenbooks newsletter
  - Follett, Ken, 1995 (Box 3)
    Profile in "The Bookseller"
  - Fontana, Dorothy, 1982 (Box 3)
  - Forward, Robert, 2002 (Box 3)
  - Forman, Joanne, 1983 (Box 3)
    Correspondence (one letter), catalog of sheet music
  - Fortschen, Bill, 1987 (Box 3)
  - Foster, Alan Dean, 1985-1987 (Box 3)
  - Fowler, Karen Joy, 1996 (Box 3)
  - Frank, Janrae, 1983-1984 (Box 3)
  - Frankowski, Leo, undated (Box 3)
    Del Rey promotional materials
  - Frayn, Michael, 2006 (Box 3)
    Q and A with "Publishers Weekly"
  - Frazetta, Frank, 1981-1995 (Box 3)
    Promotional materials, interview in "The Comics Journal," interview in "Heavy Metal"
  - Freas, Frank Kelly, 2006 (Box 3)
  - Frenkel, Jim, 1987 (Box 3)
    "BP Report"
  - Friedman, C. S., undated (Box 3)
  - Gabaldon, Diana, 1997-2006 (Box 3)
  - Gaimon, Neil, 2003-2004 (Box 3)
    Profiles in "Publishers Weekly" and "Starlog"
  - Gallun, Raymond Z., 1986-1989 (Box 3)
    Obituaries for Rhoda Katerinsky (Ricky Slavin) and Bertha Erickson Gallun
  - Gardner, John, 1982 (Box 3)
  - Garner, Alan, 1988 (Box 3)
  - Garnett, David S., 1978 (Box 3)
  - Gary, Romain, 1980-1981 (Box 3)
    Obituaries, clippings
  - Gaughan, Jack, 1985 (Box 3)
    Correspondence (one letter), reminiscence from Ben Bova
  - Gedge, Pauline, 1994 (Box 3)
  - Geis, Dick, 2005 (Box 3)
    Interview in "Paperback Parade," printed-out article from "The Oregonian"
  - Gemmell, David, 1998 (Box 3)
    Interview in "Del Rey Internet Newsletter"
  - Van Gelder, Gordon, 2003 (Box 3)
    Interview in "The New York Times"
  - Gerrold, David, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Gernsback, Hugo, 1990-2006 (Box 3)
    Profile in "Smithsonian"
  - Ghosh, Amitav, 1996-1997 (Box 3)
  - Gibson, William, 1985-2007 (Box 3)
    Promotional materials, clippings
  - Giger, H. R., 1981-1988 (Box 3)
    Clippings, flyer for signing
  - Gijsen, Wim, undated (Box 3)
  - Gilbert, Robert E., 1989 (Box 3)
    "SFC Bulletin"
  - Gilbert, Sheila, 1966-1986 (Box 3)
    Correspondence, manuscript drafts, two photographs
  - Gingrich, Newt, undated (Box 3)
    "1945" book jacket
  - Gleason, Robert, 1990 (Box 3)
  - Gloss, Molly, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Godwin, Parke, 1988 (Box 3)
  - Gakov, Vladmir, 1983 (Box 3)
    Correspondence, manuscript drafts
  - Golding, William, undated (Box 3)
  - Goodkind, Terry, 2005 (Box 3)
    Profile in Starlog
  - Gordischer, Angelica, 1989 (Box 3)
    Correspondence (one letter from Claudiomar Noguerol)
  - Gorey, Edward, 1982-2000 (Box 3)
    "Publishers Weekly" interview, obituary, bibliography
  - Goto, Hiromi, undated (Box 3)
    Page from Red Deer Press book catalog
  - Gotschalk, Peter, 1985 (Box 3)
  - Gottfried, Chet, 1984 (Box 3)
    Correspondence (one letter), clipping
  - Gottlieb, Phyllis, 1982 (Box 3)
  - Gottlieb, Robert, 1994 (Box 3)
    "The Art of Editing" interview in "The Paris Review"
  - Gottlieb, Sherry, 1974-1989 (Box 3)
    "Publishers Weekly" article
  - Goulart, Ron, 1977 (Box 3)
    Correspondence (one letter), newsletter
  - Grann, Phyllis, 1986-1996 (Box 3)
  - Grant, Charles L., 1981 (Box 3)
  - Grass, Gunter, 1996-2000 (Box 3)
  - Gray, Alasdair, 1982 (Box 3)
  - Greeley, Andrew, 1987 (Box 3)
  - Green, Roland, 1982 (Box 3)
  - Green, Simon, 1994 (Box 3)
  - Greene, Graham, 1991 (Box 3)
  - Groteboer, Jeff, 1993 (Box 3)
    Correspondence (letter from Doris Wenzel, publisher), clipping
  - Grubb, Davis, undated (Box 3)
    Book jacket for "Ancient Lights"
  - Grundy, Stephen, 1995 (Box 3)
    Article in "The Bookseller"
  - Gunn, James, 1983 (Box 3)
    Correspondence (one brief letter), book cover for "The Joy Makers," copies of "Science Fiction in the Eighties" and "The Year in Science Fiction" articles
  - Gunnarsson, Thorarinn, 1992-1994 (Box 3)
    Correspondence (one from Gunnarsson, several from Michael Stackpole), FOIA requests
  - Gurney, James, 1958-2002 (Box 3)
    Correspondence, samples of artwork, profile in "Starlog"
  - Gutheridge, George, 1982 (Box 3)
  - Gwinn, Beth, 2009 (Box 3)
  - Hacker, Andrew, 1985 (Box 3)
  - Haggard, Rider H., 1979 (Box 3)
    Correspondence (two brief letters from Lee Pritzker and Rachel Holmen)
  - Haldeman, Gay and Joe, 1991 (Box 3)
    Photograph, "How to Get a Job Like Mine" essay
  - Hall, Melissa Mia, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Haig, Matt, 2006 (Box 3)
  - Hamling, William, 1990 (Box 3)
    "Paperback Parde" Number 20
  - Handler, Daniel, 2006 (Box 3)
    Photograph, clipping
  - Harbinson, W. A., 1992 (Box 3)
    Promotional pamphlet
  - Harding, Lee, 1986 (Box 3)
    Correspondence (one letter), promotional material
  - Hardy, Lyndon, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Hariharan, Githa, 1996 (Box 3)
  - Harris, Deborah, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Harris, Robert, 1995 (Box 3)
  - Harrison, Harry, 1980-1985 (Box 3)
    Correspondence, book cover for "Skyfall," "Writer's Corner" draft for Locus
  - Harrison, Sue, undated (Box 3)
    Flyer for "Brother Wind"
  - Hartwell, Allison and David, 1982-1983 (Box 3)
    Press release, "Publishers Weekly" interview, "The Golden Age of Science Fiction 12" article
  - Hawking, Stephen M., 1990 (Box 3)
    "The J. Lloyd Eaton Collection" newsletter
  - Hawkins, Ward, undated (Box 3)
  - Heinlein, Robert A., 1961-2007; 5 folders (Box 3)
    Correspondence (including three letters from Robert Heinlein and many letters by Virginia "Ginny" Heinlein), clippings, obituaries, remembrances, promotional materials, travel notes (including an account of their trip to China written by Ye Yonglie)
  - Helprin, Mark, 1991 (Box 3)
    Entry in "Current Biography"
  - Herbert, Frank, 1979-1986 (Box 3)
    Correspondence (one brief letter, one letter about the passing of his wife, Beverly Herbert), clippings, obituaries, remembrances, promotional materials
  - Herbert, James, 1985 (Box 3)
    Page from "The Bookseller"
  - Herbert, Rosemary, 1989 (Box 3)
    article in "Publishers Weekly"
  - Hertz, John, 2017 (Box 3)
  - Hildebrandt, Greg and Tim, 1979-1996 (Box 3)
    article in "Publishers Weekly," promotional materials
  - Hill, Douglas, 1986 (Box 3)
    Book covers for "The Caves of Klydor" and "Colsec Rebellion"
  - Hillerman, Tony, 1988 (Box 3)
    Photograph, interview in "Publishers Weekly"
  - Hoban, Russell, 1981-1982 (Box 3)
  - Hodge, Brian, 1998 (Box 3)
    Interview in "Locus"
  - Hoffman, Alice, 2005 (Box 3)
  - Hinton, S. E., 2005 (Box 3)
  - Hjortsberg, William, undated (Box 3)
    "Nevermore" book jacket
  - Hogan, James, 1978 (Box 3)
  - Holdstock, Robert, 1999-2004 (Box 3)
    Interview in "Science Fiction Weekly"
  - Holland, Cecelia, 1992-1997 (Box 3)
    Correspondence, "Publishers Weekly" interview
  - Hoppe, Stephanie T, 1985 (Box 3)
  - Hopkinson, Nalo, undated (Box 3)
    Thank you note
  - Horton, Rich, 2006 (Box 3)
  - Horwood, William, undated (Box 3)
  - Howard, Robert E., 1979-2006 (Box 3)
  - Howe, James, 1984 (Box 3)
  - L. Ron Hubbard, 1972-1990 (Box 3)
    Correspondence (a few letters from others regarding Hubbard), promotional materials, clippings
  - Hull, Betty Ann, 1988-1996 (Box 3)
    Correspondence (one letter), "Elect Elizabeth Anne Hull" pamphlet, bio
  - Hunter, Evan, 2001 (Box 3)
    Tribute in "Mystery Scene"
  - Hyman, Robin, 1987 (Box 3)
  - Ing, Dean, 1981-1987 (Box 3)
  - Jackson, Rob, 1982 (Box 3)
  - Jacques, Brian, 2001 (Box 3)
    Profile in "Publishers Weekly," promotional materials
  - Jacobs, Harvey, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Jakes, John, 1978-1988 (Box 3)
    Correspondence (two brief letters), entry in "Current Biography"
  - Jakubowski, Maxim, 1983 (Box 3)
  - James, Peter, 1994 (Box 3)
  - Jason, Ben, 1963-2003 (Box 3)
    Correspondence, obituary, estate information
  - Jenkins, Harry, 1979 (Box 3)
  - Jeter, K. W., 1986 (Box 3)
    Correspondence (one brief letter), profile in "Forced Exposure"
  - Jeschke, Wolfgang, 1990 (Box 3)
    Draft of "Guest of Honor Speech" for Confiction 1990
  - Jianzhong, Guo, 1991-1993 (Box 3)
    Correspondence (one letter and one holiday card), "The Rise and Fall of Science Fiction in China" essay
  - Jones, Diane Wynne, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Jones, Jeffrey, 1987 (Box 3)
    Clippings, resume, sample of artwork
  - Jones, L. Q., undated (Box 3)
  - Jordan, Robert, 2000-2005 (Box 3)
    Correspondence (one letter), promotional materials, interview notes
  - Justor, Norman, 2001 (Box 3)
    Interview in "Salon"
  - Kantner, Paul, 1985 (Box 3)
  - Kay, Guy Gavriel, 2000-2001 (Box 3)
    Correspondence (one brief email), profile in "Starlog"
  - Kearney, Paul, undated (Box 3)
  - Keeler, Harry Stephen, undated (Box 3)
  - Kelly, James Patrick, 2002 (Box 3)
    "Science Fiction Weekly" interview
  - Kelly, Mark R., 1980 (Box 3)
  - Kennedy, Patricia (Morrison), 1991 (Box 3)
  - Keyes, Daniel, 1982-1997 (Box 3)
    Correspondence (one brief fax), bio and list of works, clipping
  - Keyes, Gregory J., undated (Box 3)
  - Kidd, Virginia, 1980 (Box 3)
  - Kihn, Greg, 1998 (Box 3)
    interview in "Locus"
  - Kilworth, Garry, 1991-1993 (Box 3)
  - King, Michael, 1996 (Box 3)
    Interview in "American Bookseller"
  - King, Stephen and Tabitha, 1979-2013 (Box 4)
    Correspondence (two letters), clippings, promotional materials
  - King, Stephen, 1986-1988 (Box 4)
    "Castle Rock" newsletters
  - Kingsbury, Donald, 1981 (Box 4)
  - Kingston, Maxine Hong, 1990 (Box 4)
    Profile in "San Francisco Examiner"
  - Kinsella, W. P., 1987 (Box 4)
  - Kirk, Tim, undated (Box 4)
  - Klein, Jay Kay, 1994 (Box 4)
  - Klein, Gerard, 1986 (Box 4)
  - Knight, Damon, 1976-1987 (Box 4)
    Correspondence, clipping
  - Koontz, Dean, 1977-1998 (Box 4)
    Correspondence, clippings
  - Kornbluth, C. M., 1994-1995 (Box 4)
    "Kornblume" fanzine
  - Korshak, Erle, 1998 (Box 4)
    Correspondence (two holiday cards)
  - Korzhenevski, Alexander, 1988-1989 (Box 4)
    Report on the Aelita-89 science fiction convention in the U.S.S.R., newsletter in russian, promotional materials
  - Koster, Elaine, undated (Box 4)
  - Kotzwinkle, William, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Kovalchuk, Mike, 1984-1993 (Box 4)
  - Kozak, Ellen, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Frenkel, Roy, undated (Box 4)
  - Kube-McDowell, Michael P., 1987-1995 (Box 4)
  - Kurits, Leonid, 2005 (Box 4)
    Correspondence (one letter from Waldemar Kumming)
  - Kurland, Michael, 1974 (Box 4)
    Publishing contract with Harlequin Enterprises Limited
  - Kushner, Ellen, 1986 (Box 4)
  - Kuykendall, Karen, 1992 (Box 4)
  - Kyle, David, 1983 (Box 4)
    "Fan Guest of Honor Speech" at the 41st World Science Fiction Convention
  - L'Engle, Madeleine, 1985 (Box 4)
  - Lafferty, R. A., 1999-2003 (Box 4)
    Correspondence (one email from Elizabeth Kennington, executrix of Lafferty's estate), print out from internet fan page
  - Langford, David, 1982-1990 (Box 4)
    Correspondence, "Interzone" magazine
  - Lanier, Sterling, 1977-1991 (Box 4)
  - Lapine, Warren, 2007-2009 (Box 4)
    Correspondence (from Lapine's attorney), clippings, information about libel laws
  - Lasser, David, 1986 (Box 4)
    Correspondence (one letter from Eric Leif Davin)
  - Lawrence, Seymour, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Leach, Linda, 1982 (Box 4)
  - Le Carre, John, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Lee, Sharon, 1983 (Box 4)
  - Lee, Tanith, 1983-1997 (Box 4)
  - Le Guin, Ursula K., 1975-2004 (Box 4)
  - Leiber, Fritz, 1979-1993 (Box 4)
    Correspondence, clippings, photographic negatives
  - Leithauser, Brad, 1997 (Box 4)
  - Leonard, John, 1979 (Box 4)
  - Lessing, Doris, 1979-1994 (Box 4)
    Two photographs, clippings
  - Lethem, Jonathan, 1997-1998 (Box 4)
    Correspondence (one brief letter), print out of "Close Encounters: The Squandered Promise of Science Fiction"
  - Leventhal, Lionel, 1985 (Box 4)
  - Levin, Ira, 1991 (Box 4)
  - Lewis, C. S., 2001 (Box 4)
    "Holy War in Shadowlands" article by Scott McLemee in "The Chronicle of Higher Education"
  - Leyner, Mark, 1993 (Box 4)
  - Liberty, Lou, 1992 (Box 4)
  - Lindahn, Val Lakey, 1983 (Box 4)
    Correspondence (one letter and a wedding invitation), one photograph
  - Link, Kelly, 2005 (Box 4)
  - Lickiss, Rebecca, 2000 (Box 4)
  - Lindskold, Jane, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Lisle, Holly, 1996 (Box 4)
    Correspondence (one printout from an online discussion group)
  - Lively, Penelope, 1988-1994 (Box 4)
  - Llewelyn, Edward, 1980-1984 (Box 4)
    List of works, bio, clippings, author questionnaire, resume
  - Longyear, Barry B., 1979-1986 (Box 4)
    Correspondence (one letter from Mary Ann Drach), bio and list of works, newsletters, press release, clipping
  - Lopoff, Richard, 1977-1981 (Box 4)
    Correspondence (one letter), "The Intergalactic Reporter," clipping
  - Lord, Glenn, 1995 (Box 4)
    Correspondence (two letters), clipping
  - Lovin, Rogers, 1979-1981 (Box 4)
    Correspondence (two letters), clippings
  - Lovecraft, H. P., 1996 (Box 4)
  - Lovegrove, James, 2009 (Box 4)
  - Lowry, Lois, undated (Box 4)
  - Lowndes, Robert A., 1967 (Box 4)
  - Lucas, George, 1989 (Box 4)
    "The Lucasfilm Fan Club" magazine
  - Lundwall, Sam, 1981 (Box 4)
  - Lynn, Elizabeth, 1978 (Box 4)
    Correspondence (one letter), promotional materials
  - MacDermott, Aubrey, 1981-1983 (Box 4)
  - MacDonald, John J., 1979-1994 (Box 4)
  - MacGregor, Loren, undated (Box 4)
  - MacLeod, Ken, 2000 (Box 4)
    Correspondence (email with resume)
  - Mahaffey, Bea, 1987 (Box 4)
    Correspondence (one letter from Mrs. Jack Stichtenoth)
  - Mahy, Margaret, undated (Box 4)
  - Mailer, Norman, 2006 (Box 4)
    Reading announcement, "Publishers Weekly" interview
  - Maitz, Don, undated (Box 4)
  - Malzberg, Barry, 1977-1983 (Box 4)
  - Mann, Phillip, undated (Box 4)
    One photographic negative, page from book catalog
  - Marcellino, Fred, 1987 (Box 4)
    Profile in "Insight" magazine
  - Margolis, Esther, undated (Box 4)
  - Marlowe, Stephen, 1996 (Box 4)
  - Marquez, Gabriel Garcia, 1988-2001 (Box 4)
  - Martin, Valerie, 2006 (Box 4)
  - Martine-Barnes, Adrienne, 1983 (Box 4)
  - Matthews, Rodney, 1985 (Box 4)
  - Matthews, Susan, undated (Box 4)
  - Mattingly, David B., 1983-2009 (Box 4)
    Correspondence (two letters and holiday cards)
  - Maxwell, Robert, 1991 (Box 4)
  - May, Julian, 1982 (Box 4)
  - Mayer, Peter, 1996 (Box 4)
  - Mazuranic, Krsto, 1986 (Box 4)
  - McCaffrey, Anne, 1978-2005 (Box 4)
    Correspondence, "Annie and Horses" profile by Chelsea Quinn Yarbro
  - McCarry, Charles, 1988 (Box 4)
  - McCarty, Dennis, undated (Box 4)
  - McCarthy, Shawna, 1985 (Box 4)
  - McDonough, Thomas A., 1987 (Box 4)
  - McElderry, Margaret, 1997 (Box 4)
  - McGinnis, Robert, 1988 (Box 4)
    "Paperback Parade" number 12
  - McHugh, Maureen, 1999 (Box 4)
    Correspondence (brief email)
  - McIntosh, J. T., 1981 (Box 4)
  - Mckiernan, Dennis L., 1987-1991 (Box 4)
    Correspondence (two letters), "Accidental Author" essay
  - McKillip, Patricia, 1976 (Box 4)
  - McLaughlin, Dean, 1981 (Box 4)
    Correspondence (one letter including bio), one photograph
  - McQuay, Mike, 1987 (Box 4)
  - McQuinn, Donald, 1993-1994 (Box 4)
    Correspondence (two letters), bio
  - Meluch, Rebecca, 1996 (Box 4)
  - Meredith, Richard, 1974-1979 (Box 4)
    Correspondence (one letter from Neal Blaikie), obituaries
  - Meredith, Scott, 1985-1993 (Box 4)
    Obituaries, list of clients
  - Merril, Judith, 1992-1998 (Box 4)
    Correspondence (one letter), remembrances, photographic negatives, "Sol Rising" magazine, clipping
  - Merritt, A., 1989 (Box 4)
  - Meyer, Stephanie, 2008 (Box 4)
    Printed-out article from "Miami Herald"
  - Michener, James, undated (Box 4)
    Promotional materials for "Mexico"
  - Mieville, China, 2002 (Box 4)
    Correspondence (one email)
  - Mills, Bob, 1986 (Box 4)
    Remembrances
  - Mills, C. J., unknown (Box 4)
    Book cover for "Winter World"
  - Miller, Walter M., 1995 (Box 4)
  - Modesitt, L. E., undated (Box 4)
    "actusf" interview
  - Moffett, Judith, 1989 (Box 4)
    Correspondence (one postcard), resume
  - Moebius, Jean Giraud, undated (Box 4)
  - McEnroe, Richard, 1981 (Box 4)
    Correspondence (two letters), notes
  - Montana, Ron, 1989-1990 (Box 4)
  - Moon, Elizabeth, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Moorcock, Michael, 1978-2002 (Box 4)
    Correspondence, promotional materials, clippings, interviews
  - Moore, C.L., 1976 (Box 4)
    interview
  - More, Dennis, 1979 (Box 4)
  - Morgenstern, Erin, 2011 (Box 4)
  - Morlan, A. R., 1993 (Box 4)
  - Morressy, John, 1978-1984 (Box 4)
  - Morrissey, Dean, 2008 (Box 4)
  - Morris, Chris and Janet, 1980-1985 (Box 4)
  - Mosesson, Gloria R., 1983 (Box 4)
  - Moskowitz, Sam, 2002 (Box 4)
    One photographic postcard
  - Moss, Robert, undated (Box 4)
  - Murray, R. A., undated (Box 4)
  - Naipaul, V. S., 1994 (Box 4)
  - Nedelkovich, A., 1989-1990 (Box 4)
    Correspondence (one letter), news from Yugoslavia about science fiction, book cover for "Gregory Benford" by Vremenski Pejzaz
  - Neville, Kris, 1980 (Box 4)
    Correspondence (two letters from Roy Squires about Neville's death)
  - Nicholson, William, undated (Box 4)
  - Nicholls, Peter, 1981 (Box 4)
  - Nimoy, Leonard, 2003 (Box 4)
  - Niven, Larry, 1979-1991 (Box 4)
  - Nolan, Bill, 1984-2012 (Box 4)
  - Noon, Jeff, 1994 (Box 4)
  - Norman, John (Lange, John F. Jr.), 2007 (Box 4)
    Correspondence (one email from Dennis Lien)
  - Noguerol, Claudio Omar, 1987-1990; 2 folders (Box 4, Box 7)
    Correspondence (two letters), "Science Fiction in Argentina" essay
  - Norton, Andre, 1963-2005; 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Norwescon, 1983 (Box 4)
    Correspondence (one brief letter from David G. Hartwell), clippings
  - Nourse, Alan, 1977-1982 (Box 4)
  - Novak, Lisa, 1990 (Box 4)
  - O'Brian, Patrick, 1992 (Box 4)
  - O'Brien, Willis, 1984 (Box 4)
    Exhibition catalog
  - O'Connor, Pat, 1990 (Box 4)
    "Talk of the Trade" interview in "Publishers Weekly"
  - Offut, Andy, 1980-1982 (Box 4)
    Correspondence (one letter from Andrew Offutt, one letter from Susan Allison)
  - Oklahoma, Donna, 1989 (Box 4)
    Correspondence (one letter), two photographs
  - Oliver, Chad, 1984-1993 (Box 4)
    Correspondence (one letter from Chad Oliver, one letter from Dolores Phelps), clippings, obituaries
  - O'Neill, Pamela, undated (Box 4)
    Partial resume
  - Orwell, George, 1983 (Box 4)
    Press release, profile in "Time" magazine
  - Page, Gerald W., 1984 (Box 4)
    Correspondence (one letter from David Page), obituary
  - Pangborn, Edgar, 1984 (Box 4)
    Correspondence (one letter from Jessica Pangborn regarding Georgia Wood Pangborn), includes stories by Georgia Wood Pangborn
  - Panshin, Alexei (Cory), 1967-1978 (Box 4)
  - Passarella, Jach, undated (Box 4)
  - Peake, Mervyn, 1984 (Box 4)
    Correspondence (one letter with program for "The Rhyme of the Flying Bomb"
  - Pedler, Kit, 1981 (Box 4)
    Correspondence (one letter from Brian Aldiss and one letter from Mike Ashley), obituary
  - Pendray, Edward G, 1986 (Box 4)
  - Peters, Elizabeth, 1987 (Box 4)
  - Peterson, Gail, undated (Box 4)
    Bio and promotional materials
  - Peterson, Susan, undated (Box 4)
  - Pierce, Hayford, 1986 (Box 4)
  - Pierce, John R., 1991 (Box 4)
    Clipping, resume
  - Piper, H. Beam, 1963-1978 (Box 5)
    Correspondence, book cover for "The Fuzzy Papers," promotional materials
  - Pinckard, Tom and Terri, 1984 (Box 5)
    Correspondence (one letter from Terri Pinckard)
  - Platt, Charles, 1982-2008 (Box 5)
    Correspondence, clippings, "REM" newsletters
  - Pohl, Fred, 1967-1987 (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL11689-MCS-0001)
    Correspondence, clipping, one microcassette
    Conditions Governing Access
    Original audio materials are closed to use. Contact Research Services in advance to request the production of listening copies.
  - Pollotta, Nick, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Polikarpus, Viido, undated (Box 5)
  - Popescu, Petru, undated (Box 5)
  - Porter, Andrew, 1973 (Box 5)
  - Pournelled, Jerry, 1977-1982 (Box 5)
  - Powers, Adam, undated (Box 5)
    Photograph of action figures
  - Poyser, Victoria and Kennedy, 1985 (Box 5)
    Correspondence (three postcards)
  - Pratchett, Terry, 1988-2000 (Box 5)
  - Preuss, Paul, 1980 (Box 5)
  - Price, E. Hofferman, 1978-1982 (Box 5)
  - Priest, Chris, 1983 (Box 5)
  - Pronzini, Bill, 2008 (Box 5)
    "Publishers Weekly" review
  - Pullman, Philip, 1998-2007 (Box 5)
  - Reed, Kit, undated (Box 5)
    Correspondence (one note)
  - Reidy, Carolyn, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Renault, Mary, 1983 (Box 5)
  - Repp, Ed Earl, 1979 (Box 5)
  - Reynolds, Alastair, 2005 (Box 5)
  - Reynolds, Mack, 1982 (Box 5)
    Correspondence (two letters), obituary of William P. McGivern, obituary of Mack Reynolds
  - Rice, Anne, 1986-2000 (Box 5)
  - Richardson, Robert S., 1981 (Box 5)
  - Riley, Judith Merkle, undated (Box 5)
  - Robbins, Trina, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Roberts, Jane, 2006 (Box 5)
  - Roberts, Keith, 1987 (Box 5)
    Interview, "Small Press -- The Last Resort" article draft
  - Roberts, Nora, 2002-2004 (Box 5)
    Clipping, partial book cover
  - Robinette, Steve, 1977 (Box 5)
  - Robinson, Kim Stanley, 2000s (Box 5)
  - Robinson, Spider and Jeanne, 1980-1997 (Box 5)
  - Roddenberry, Gene, 1987 (Box 5)
    "Star Trek: The Official Fan Club" issue 57
  - Rogers, Alva, unknown (Box 5)
  - Rogers, Hubert, 1982 (Box 5)
    Correspondence (two brief letters about Rogers's obituary)
  - Rohan, Michael Scott, undated (Box 5)
  - Roszak, Theodore, 1995 (Box 5)
  - Roth, Philip, 2006 (Box 5)
  - Rotsler, William, 1975 (Box 5)
    "KTEIC" magazine
  - Rottensteiner, Franz, 1996 (Box 5)
  - Rowley, Christopher, 1995 (Box 5)
  - Rowling, J. K., 1998-2001 (Box 5)
  - Rucker Rudy, 1980-1989 (Box 5)
    Correspondence, clipping, promotional materials
  - Rushdie, Salman, 1989-2000; 4 folders (Box 5)
    Correspondence (brief letters about Rushdie), mostly clippings
  - Rusch, Kristine Kathryn, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Russ, Joanna, 1973-1994 (Box 5)
    Correspondence (one letter), profile in "LAMBDA Book Report," copy of "Somebody's Trying to Kill Me and I Think It's My Husband: The Modern Gothic"
  - Russell, Mary Doria, 1996-2005 (Box 5)
    Promotional materials, profile in "Publishers Weekly"
  - Russell, Ray, 1977-1999 (Box 5)
  - Ryan, Alan, 1980-1982 (Box 5)
  - Ryman, Geoff, 2004 (Box 5)
    Interview in "Infinity Plus"
  - Rypel, Ted C., 1983 (Box 5)
  - Saberhagen, Fred, 1979-1984 (Box 5)
    Correspondence (one brief letter), flyer, clippings
  - Sadler, Barry, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Sagan, Carl, 1981-1994 (Box 5)
    Correspondence (one brief letter), clippings, promotional pamphlet
  - Sailor, Charles, 1979 (Box 5)
    Press releases
  - Saint H. F., 1987 (Box 5)
  - Sallis, James, 1988 (Box 5)
  - Salmonson, Jessica, 1981-1982 (Box 5)
  - Sargent, Pamela, 1994 (Box 5)
  - Saramago, Jose, 2001-2007 (Box 5)
  - Saul, John, undated (Box 5)
    Book cover for "Hell Fire"
  - Saunders, Charles, 1981 (Box 5)
  - Scalzi, John, 2012 (Box 5)
    Clippings, interview
  - Scarborough, Elizabeth Ann, 1986-1989 (Box 5)
    Correspondence (one letter from Betty L. Scarborough", promotional materials
  - Schenck, Hilbert, undated (Box 5)
    Book cover for "At the Eye of the Ocean"
  - Schiff, Stuart, 1982 (Box 5)
  - Schoenherr, John, 1988 (Box 5)
  - Scholz, Carter, 2004 (Box 5)
  - Schow, David, 1982 (Box 5)
  - Schwartz, Julius, 1974-1990 (Box 5)
    Correspondence, clippings, two photographic postcards
  - Scortia, Tom, 1978 (Box 5)
  - Scott, Melissa, 1985 (Box 5)
  - Self, Will, undated (Box 5)
  - Sendak, Maurice, 1981-2006 (Box 5)
    Clippings, bio
  - Sharp, George, 1980-1983 (Box 5)
    Art samples
  - Sharra, Michael, undated (Box 5)
  - Shaw, Bob, 1981 (Box 5)
    Correspondence (one postcard)
  - Shea, Michael, 1983 (Box 5)
  - Sheckley, Robert, 1977-1998 (Box 5)